

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthday : 7th June 1991
Relationship : Married
Nationality : Bangladeshi
Languages : English, Bengali

SKILLS

COMMUNICATION CREATIVITY TEAMWORK ORGANIZATION LEADERSHIP

SOFTWARE

MS Office Mac OSX Pages Mac OSX Keynote MYOB SAP

CONTACT



01615001030



sazal.alam@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sazal-alam



1/11, Pallabi, Dhaka Bangladesh.

Sazal Alam

Accounting and Finance Graduate

PROFILE

An organized, detail-oriented and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks and stay calm under pressure; experienced in a wide range of fields such as Accounting and Finance, Administration, Marketing and Customer Service.

Education

Bachelor's in Accounting & Financial Management

La Trobe University Sydney, CBD, NSW 2013 - 2017 Foundation of Business Studies

La Trobe University Sydney, CBD, NSW 2012 - 2013 O'levels & A'levels

Jun 2017- Apr 2019

Jul 2016- Sep 2016

GCE Academy Mirpur, Dhaka 2009 - 2012

Experience

The Little Paris (Administration Officer)

<u>Duties</u>: Employee Expense System, Client Service, Online marketing, Prepare ad-hoc reports and Reconciliations.

Nokia Networks (Accounts Payable Intern)

<u>Duties</u>: Assist in operation of the payable, Employee Expense system, Prepare bureau of statistics form and reports, general ledger reconciliation, reconcile inter-company billing and inter-unit collections, ad-hoc, ESS statements and Corporate credit card management.

La Trobe University (Orientation Coordinator)

<u>Duties</u>: Register new students, organize tours for new students, assist on academic intakes and provide counseling.

Woolworths Supermarkets

Duties: Cashier, Stock take, Customer service.

Jan 2015- Jun 2015

Feb 2013- Oct 2014

REFERENCE

Demi Xu

Chief Accounts officer Asia-Pacific Nokia Networks T. +6 1497 732 982 E. demi.xu@nokia.com Vivek Sha

Former Manager
The Little Paris
T. +6 1417 403 916
E. vivekshah v@hotmail.com